myunplug.com 2012-07-29

# MyUnplug.com - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

 **What information do we collect?**
  * We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.
  * Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.
  * We collect information about pages you visit on the site

**What do we use your information for?**
  * Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
  * To personalize your experience.
  * To improve our website
  * To improve customer service
  * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent
  * To post on your wall, save photo on your album and tag on your photo

**How do we protect your information?**
  * We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information 
  * These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**
  * We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information without your consent. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential, use it only for the purpose of our site, and delete it upon our request. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**
  * Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**
  * We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**
  * This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**
  * By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**
  * If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This policy was last modified on 27/01/2012
